haier.com 2015-06-13

# Privacy Policy | Haier America

Haier America respects your privacy and has instituted policies that are intended to ensure that any personal information that you provide to us is handled in a safe and responsible manner.

It is unnecessary to provide personal information in order to gain access to or browse our website. Personal information may be collected in various forms including product registrations, purchasing extended service agreements, e-mail messages, and requests for information from Haier America. By using our website, you consent to the collection and use of this information by Haier America.

For your protection, Haier America does not sell, trade or rent the customer information provided to us to third parties. However, we may use personally identifiable information provided by visitors to fulfill the purpose for which such information was provided, as described by this Policy, and as disclosed at the time the visitor information is requested. Haier America or one of our affiliate companies may use personal information collected for internal marketing purposes such as market research. It may also be used to contact you about the latest product information or special promotions.

A technology called "cookies" may be used to provide you with tailored information. A cookie is a small data file that a website can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your hard drive so that we can recognize you when you return. Cookies do not alter your hard drive in any way and cannot be used to access any personal information from your computer.

Although it is our hope that you find the display of advertising to you based on your anonymous interests valuable, if you would prefer not to participate in the services offered through these solutions, you can always opt-out of this activity by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) website by clicking  
<http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>. 

Important Note:

Haier America is committed to protecting the safety and privacy of children using the internet. This site is not intended for persons under 13 years of age. By entering this site, users verify that they are 13 years of age or older. In keeping with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, we will never knowingly request personal identification information from children under the age of 13.

##  Disclaimer:

This statement is subject to revision without prior notification. Haier America may contain links to other websites and is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of other websites.
